Guide to the Robert H. Foote papers, 1939-2006.
Foote, Robert H. papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert H. Foote papers, 1939-2006.
21-14-2668
Robert H. Foote
13.3 cubic ft.
Manuscripts, Photographs, Publications, Reports, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes publications, reports, subject files, course material, articles, video tape, audio tapes, and photograph.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Jacob Gould Schurman professor of animal science, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes publications, reports, subject files, course material, and proceedings of the Cornell Symposium on Theriogenology honoring Foote, 1992; "Artificial Insemination to Cloning: Tracing 50 Years of Research," 1998; reprint of "Development of Reproductive Biotechnologies in Domestic Animals from Artificial Insemination to Cloning: A Perspective," in Cloning, Vol. 1, Number 3, 1999; Proceedings of the International Symposium: "From the first artificial insemination to the modern reproduction biotechnologies: traditional ways and new frontiers of animal production, Regio Emilia (Italy) October 8-9,1999;" "Highlights in Dairy Cattle Reproduction in the Last 100 Years," 2005. Also articles, video tape, audio tapes, and photograph.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Foote, Robert H.; Cornell University--Faculty.
Subjects:
Animal breeding.; Theriogenology.; Cloning.; Artificial insemination.; Artificial insemination--Cattle.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also: Internet First University Press: Animal Reproduction: Reflections by Robert H. Foote, 2006
CONTAINER LIST
- Reports and Papers (Box 1)
- Publications List: Foote and Coworkers Laboratory of Animal Breeding and Artificial Insemination (Box 1)
- Research Grants - Biotech Steamcell, 1958 - 1970 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1980s - 2000 (Box 1)
- Growth and Reproductive Physiology of the Rabbit, 1972 - 1986 (Box 1)
- Reference Lists (Box 1)
- CD of Photos - "100 Year History of Reproductive Physiology" (Box 1)
- Reprints, 1940 - 2003 (Box 2)
- Subject Files (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Notebooks, 1950 - 1991 (Box 3)
- Subject Files, 1970s - 2006 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Reports, Correspondence (Box 4)
- Dept. of Animal Science - CSRS Review, 1994 (Box 4)
- A Self-Study of the Dept. of Animal Science - External Review and Department Response, 1999 (Box 4)
- Biographical Information - "Born to Live and Living to Learn" Autobiography, 2003 (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous Slides (Box 5)
- Video on Cloning - by Jerry Yang (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous Slides, 1970s - 2006 (Box 6)
- Subject Files (Box 6)
- Correspondence (Box 6)
- Subject Files, 1960s - 2001 (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous Slides (Box 7)
- Course Materials- Animal Science 220, 430, 1950s - 1980s (Box 8)
- Reference Lists, 1954 - 1991 (Box 9)
- Course Materials - Animal Science 430, 431, 497 (Box 9)
- Course Materials - Undergraduate Research and Unpublished Research, 1950s - 2002 (Box 10)
- Unpublished Research (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous Notebooks (Box 11)
- Unpublished Research (Box 12)
- Course Materials - Animal Science 220, 321, 370, 430, 431, 494, 718, 1960 - 2005 (Box 12)
- Physiological and Technical Aspects of Animal Reproduction - Robert Foote, 1974 (Box 12)
- List of Publications from the Lab of Animal Breeding and Artificial Insemination, 1939 - 1985 (Box 12)
- Animal Science Dept. - Graduate Alumni News, 1998 - 2006 (Box 12)
- Course Materials - Animal Science 220, 430 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Summaries and Reports, 1950 - 1992 (Box 13)
- Videos, etc. (Box 14)